A Guide to the Virginia Auditor of Public Accounts - Tobacco and Flour Inspector Records, 1776-1878
Library of Virginia
- Series IX: Public Tobacco Warehouse vouchers, 1776-1865 (APA 293)., Extent: XX cubic feet. (Box XX-XX)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1785 Oct 31. (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1785 Nov 5. (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1785 Nov 12. (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Vouchers (Mantapike Warehouse), 1785 Nov 18. (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Hole Warehouse), 1785 Nov 22. (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Vouchers (Dumfries Warehouse), 1785 Nov 28. (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Vouchers (Cottage Landing Warehouse), 1785 Dec 1. (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1785 Dec 6. (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Vouchers (College Landing Warehouse), 1786 Jan 16. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Gray's Creek Warehouse), 17886 Feb 1. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Lowpoint Warehouse), 1786 Feb 1. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1786 Feb 10. (Box 3, Folder 2.5)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1786 Feb 10. (Box 3, Folder 2.5)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1786 Feb 9. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Mantapike Warehouse), 1786 Mar 18. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Todd's Warehouse), 1786 Apr 8. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1786 Apr 14. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Denbigh Warehouse), 1786 June 15. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1786 June 17. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Kemp's Warehouse), 1786 June 21. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1786 June 24. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Portsmouth Warehouse), 1786 June 28. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1786 Oct 13. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1786 Oct 18. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Indian Creek Warehouse), 1786 Nov 6. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Meriwether's Warehouse), 1786 Nov 6. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1786 Dec 20. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Turner's Warehouse), 1786 Dec 20. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Portsmouth Warehouse), 1787 Jan 13. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1787 Jan 20. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1787 Feb 15. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1787 Mar 14. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1787 Apr 6. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1787 Apr 24. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1787 June 9. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1787 June 18. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1787 June 18. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1787 June 23. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1787 July 3. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Aylett's Warehouse), 1787 July 6. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Bowler's Warehouse), 1787 Aug 15. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Falls of Potomac Warehouse), 1787 Sept 20. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Portsmouth Warehouse), 1787 Oct 1. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1787 Sept 4. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Meriwether's Warehouse), 1787 Oct 3. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Suffolk Warehouse), 1787 Oct 23. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Meriwether's Warehouse), 1787 Nov 2. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Crow's Warehouse), 1787 Nov 21. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1788 Mar 14. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1788 Mar 14. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1788 Mar 25. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Pocomoke Warehouse), 1788 Apr 2. (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1788 Apr 8. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Hobb's Hole Warehouse), 1788 Apr 28. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Todd's Warehouse), 1788 May 1. (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Hobb's Hole Warehouse), 1788 May 6. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1788 June 2. (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1788 June 3. (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Nominy Warehouse), 1788 July 31. (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Bowler's Warehouse), 1788 Aug 28. (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Mattox Warehouse), 1788 Sept 4. (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1788 Sept 16. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1788 Oct 1. (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Totusky's Warehouse), 1788 Oct 14. (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1788 Oct 18. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Pocomoke Warehouse), 1788 Nov 8. (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1788 Nov 11. (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Quantico Warehouse), 1788 Nov 15. (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1788 Nov 13. (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Dumfries Warehouse), 1788 Nov 13. (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Bowler's Warehouse), 1788 Nov 29. (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Crow's Warehouse), 1788 Dec 6. (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Mantapike Warehouse), 1788 Dec 12. (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1788 Dec 15. (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1789 Jan 7. (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1789 Jan 9. (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1789 Jan 14. (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1789 Jan 26. (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Bowler's Warehouse), 1789 Feb 17. (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Totusky Warehouse), 1789 Mar 18. (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (York Warehouse), 1789 Mar 18. (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Glasscock's Warehouse), 1789 May 6. (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1789 May 7. (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1789 May 15. (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1789 June 5. (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Vouchers (Bollingbrook Warehouse), 1789 June 8. (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Vouchers (Gibson's Warehouse), 1789 June 8. (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1789 June 12. (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Vouchers (Totusky Warehouse), 1789 June 24. (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Vouchers (Urbana Warehouse), 1789 July 2. (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Vouchers (Pungoteague Warehouse), 1789 July 17. (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouse), 1789 July 27. (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1789 Aug 8. (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's and Shockoe Warehouse), 1789 Sept 9. (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1789 Oct 7. (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1789 Oct 9. (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Vouchers (Totusky Warehouse), 1789 Oct 12. (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Vouchers (Littlepage's Warehouse), 1789 Oct 16. (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Vouchers (Meriwether's Warehouse), 1789 Oct 19. (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Vouchers (Indian Creek Warehouse), 1789 Oct 20. (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Vouchers (Curd's Warehouse), 1789 Oct 26. (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Vouchers (Suffolk Warehouse), 1789 Nov 24. (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Vouchers (Swan Creek Warehouse), 1789 Dec 11. (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Vouchers (Swan Creek Warehouse), 1789 Dec 18. (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Vouchers (Scott's and Frankford's Warehouse), 1789 Dec 22. (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1790 Feb 3. (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1790 Feb 17. (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Vouchers (Nominy Warehouse), 1790 Apr 13. (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1790 Apr 22. (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1790 Apr 22. (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Vouchers (Ware's Warehouse), 1790 Apr 26. (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1790 Oct 12. (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Vouchers (College Landing Warehouse), 1790 Oct 30. (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1790 Nov 12. (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Vouchers (Hickman Warehouse - Mercer County), 1790 Nov 13. (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1790 Dec 9. (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1790 Dec 11. (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Vouchers (Aquia Warehouse), 1790 Dec 24. (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1791 Feb 2. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's Warehouse), 1791 Feb 21. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1791 Mar 14. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Aquia Warehouse), 1791 Mar 21. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Nominy Warehouse), 1791 Mar 21. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1791 Mar 25. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Hobb's Hole Warehouse), 1791 Apr 29. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Dymer's Warehouse), 1791 May 6. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1791 May 18. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse - Hemp), 1791 June 14. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1791 June 20. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1791 Oct 7. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1791 Oct 11. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1791 Oct 19. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1791 Oct 19. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Harrod's Landing Warehouse), 1791 Oct 25. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Stuart's Creek Warehouse), 1791 Oct 26. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Walton's Warehouse), 1791 Oct 26. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Mantapike Warehouse), 1791 Oct 27. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Deep Creek Warehouse), 1791 Nov 2. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1791 Nov 4. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Falls of the Potomac Warehouse), 1791 Nov 5. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1791 Nov 7. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Hobb's Hole Warehouse), 1791 Nov 8. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Campbell's Warehouse), 1791 Nov 10. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Stuart's Creek Warehouse), 1791 Nov 10. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1791 Nov 16. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1791 Nov 17. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehouses), 1791 Nov 24. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse - Hemp), 1791 Nov 24. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1791 Nov 29. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Bollingbrook's, Cedarpoint, Petersburg and Westbrook Warehouses), 1791 Dec 5. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1791 Dec 7. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Barksdale's Warehouse), 1791 Dec 23. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Unknown Warehouse), 1792 Jan 2. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1792 Jan 2. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1792 Jan 5. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1792 Jan 7. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehouses), 1792 Jan 17. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Rocky Ridge Warehouse), 1792 Mar 13. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Nicholas' Warehouse), 1792 Mar 28. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Frankfort Warehouse), 1792 May 11. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehouses), 1792 May 15. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1792 May 18. (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Deacon's Neck Warehouse), 1792 May 19. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1792 June 13. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (High Street Warehouse), 1792 Jun 29. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Westhill Warehouse), 1792 June 29. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Aylett's Warehouse), 1792 July 9. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Gibson's Warehouse), 1792 July 14. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Gibson's Warehouse), 1792 July 24. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Todd's Warehouse), 1792 Aug 18. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1792 Sept 5. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse - Hemp), 1792 Sept 11. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1792 Sept 19. (Box 4, Folder 48.5)
  - Vouchers (Woodson's Warehouse), 1792 Oct 3. (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1792 Oct 10. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (High Street Warehouse), 1792 Oct 11. (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1792. (Box 4)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1792 Nov 6. (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Indian Creek Warehouse), 1792 Nov 9. (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Nominy Warehouse), 1792 Nov 17. (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1792 Nov 17. (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Shepherd's Warehouse), 1792 Nov 20. (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Totusky Warehouse), 1792 Nov 21. (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Unknown Warehouse), 1792 Nov 28. (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Dumfries Warehouse), 1792 Nov 30. (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1792 Dec 5. (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehouses), 1792 Dec 11. (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1793 Feb 9. (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (St. Taminy Warehouse), 1793 Feb 11. (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Quantico Warehouse), 1793 Mar 21. (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Quantico Warehouse), 1793 Mar 25. (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Richmond Warehouse - Hemp), 1793 July 8. (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Blandford's, Boyd's and Davis' Warehouses), 1797 Oct 11. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1797 Oct 13. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Blandford's, Boyd's and Davis' Warehouses), 1797 Oct 14. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Rockett's, and Shockoe Warehouses), 1797 Oct 14. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's Warehouse), 1797 Oct 16. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1797 Oct 21. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's Warehouse), 1797 Oct 27. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1797 Nov 10. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Blandford's, Petersburg, and Pocahontas Warehouses), 1798 Jan 11. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehousew), 1798 Jan 19. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Page's Warehouse), 1798 Jan 25. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1798 Mar 23. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Camden's Warehouse), 1798 Mar 29. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1798Mar 30. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Colchester Warehouse), 1798 Apr 2. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg and Spring Warehouses), 1798 Apr 5. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Barksdale's, Brook, Osborne's and Pocahontas Warehouses), 1798 May 3. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1798 May 21. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (John Bollin's Warehouse), 1798 June 12. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Manchester Warehouse), 1798 July 3. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Buckingham County Warehouses), 1798 July 30. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouse), 1798 Aug 1. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Dixon's, Fredericksburg and Royston's Warehouses), 1798 Sept 24. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth's and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1798 Sept 24. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Buckingham County Warehouses), 1798 Sept 24. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Hole, Gibson's, and Machodack Warehouses), 1798 Sept 27. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Commissioner), 1798 Sept 29. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Dunkirk Warehouse), 1798 Oct 1. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Rosegill Warehouse), 1798 Oct 3. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Manchester, and Trent's Warehouse), 1798 Oct 13. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1798 Oct 16. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Townes Warehouse), 1798 Nov 28. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Unknown Warehouse), 1798 Dec 1. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1798 Dec 13. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Totusky Warehouse), 1799 Jan 4. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Gibson's Warehouse), 1799 Jan 17. (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1799 Jan 21. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg and Spring Warehouses), 1799 Jan 28. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Camden's, Migginson, and Tye River Warehouses), 1799 Feb 1. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1799 Feb 7. (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1799 Feb 12. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1799 Feb 12. (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg and Spring Warehouses), 1799 Feb 18. (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1799 Feb 19. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1799 Feb 20. (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Deane's Warehouse), 1799 Feb 26. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1799 Mar 15. (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Mantapike Warehouse), 1799 Mar 18. (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Todd's Warehouse), 1799 Mar 26. (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1799 May 7. (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1799 May 11. (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1799 June 5. (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Woodson's Warehouse), 1799 June 13. (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Todd's Warehouse), 1799 June 24. (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Anderson's Warehouse), 1799 June 27. (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1799 July 10. (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1799 Aug 6. (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1799 Sept 5. (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Buckingham County Warehouses), 1799 Sept 19. (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg and Spring Warehouses), 1799 Sept 23. (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouses), 1799 Sept 24. (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1799 Sept 27. (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehouses), 1799 Oct 3. (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouse), 1799 Oct 9. (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehouse), 1799 Oct 23. (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1799 Oct 29. (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's and Nicholas' Warehouses), 1799 Nov 14. (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Hole and Gibson's Warehouses), 1799 Nov 19. (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Vouchers (Gibson's Warehouse), 1799 Nov 30. (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1799 Dec 4. (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Vouchers (Fluvanna County Warehouses), 1799 Dec 9. (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Vouchers (Dymer's Warehouse), 1799 Dec 19. (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1799 Dec 21. (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Vouchers (Falmouth and Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1799 Dec 16. (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Vouchers (Royston's Warehouse), 1800 Jan 13. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Vouchers (Randolph's Warehouse), 1800 Jan 25. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's and Trent's Warehouses), 1800 Feb 19. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Vouchers (Royston's Warehouse), 1800 Mar 8. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1800 Mar 17. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1800 Mar 17. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Vouchers (Mantapike Warehouse), 1800 May 20. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1800 June 7. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Vouchers (Fredericksburg Warehouse), 1800 Sept 23. (Box 6, Folder 7.5)
  - Vouchers (Dixon, Fredericksburg, and Royston's Warehouses), 1800 Sept 30. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's, Rockett's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1800 Oct 13. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Vouchers (Aylett's Warehouse), 1800 Oct 15. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's and Horsley's Warehouses), 1800 Nov 12. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Vouchers (Camden's, New Market and Swann's Creek Warehouse), 1800 Nov 10. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouses), 1800 Nov 14. (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Hole, Machodack and Port Conway Warehouses), 1800 Nov 18. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1800 Dec 3. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Vouchers (Dinwiddie County Warehouses), 1800. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg and Spring Warehouses), 1800 Dec 16. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Trent's and Manchester Warehouses), 1800 Dec 27. (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Vouchers (Coan's Warehouse), 1801 Jan 19. (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1801 Feb 11. (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Vouchers (Lynch's Warehouse), 1801 Feb 25. (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's Warehouse), 1801 Mar 2. (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Vouchers (Trent's Warehouse), 1801 Mar 10. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1801 Mar 16. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Vouchers (Prince George County Warehouses), 1801 Mar 17. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Vouchers (Byrd's and Shockoe Warehouses), 1801 Apr 4. (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1801 Apr 16. (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Vouchers (John Bolling's Warehouse), 1801 May 13. (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1801 May 18. (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Vouchers (Aylett's Warehouse), 1801 May 20. (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1801 June 3. (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Vouchers (Royston's Warehouse), 1801 June 9. (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's Warehouse), 1801 June 13. (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1801 June 22. (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1801 July 8. (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's Warehouse), 1801 July 10. (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1801 July 13. (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1801 Sept 11. (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Vouchers (Prince George County Warehouses), 1801 Sept 29. (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Vouchers (Mantapike Warehouse), 1801 Oct 1. (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Vouchers (Essex County Warehouses), 1801 Oct 5. (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1801 Oct 6. (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1801 Oct 6. (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Vouchers (Gibson's Warehouse), 1801 Oct 10. (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's, Manchester and Trent's Warehouses), 1801 Oct 17. (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Vouchers (Cannon's Warehouse), 1801 Oct 26. (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Vouchers (Lynchburg and Spring Warehouses), 1801 Oct 28. (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Vouchers (Boyd's Hole, Machodack, and Port Conway Warehouses), 1801 Nov 2. (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's Warehouse), 1801 Nov 2. (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Vouchers (Johnson's Warehouse), 1801 Nov 10. (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Vouchers (Petersburg Warehouse), 1801 Nov 11. (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Vouchers (Rivanna Warehouse), 1801 Dec 14. (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Spring Warehouse), 1801 Dec 14. (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Vouchers (Camden's, Swann Creek and Tye River Warehouses), 1801 Dec 16. (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1801 Dec 11. (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Vouchers (Northumberland County Warehouses), 1801 Dec 31. (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Vouchers (Lancaster County Warehouses), 1802 Jan 14. (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Vouchers (Wicomico Warehouse), 1802 Jan 28. (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1802. (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Vouchers (Shockoe Warehouse), 1802 Mar 6. (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Vouchers (Rosegill and Urbanna Warehouses), 1802 Apr 30. (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Vouchers (Dunkirk Warehouse), 1802 May 8. (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Vouchers (Colchester Warehouse), 1802 May 31. (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1802 July 24. (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Vouchers (Rockett's Warehouse), 1802 Sept 8. (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Vouchers (Horsley's Warehouse), 1802 Sept 22. (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Vouchers (Henderson's Warehouse), 1802 Sept 29. (Box 6, Folder 64)